import { Category } from 'src/app/interfaces/category.interface';

export default {
  name: 'Базовые',
  cards: [
    {
      question: 'zdrAvo',
      answer: 'Здравствуйте',
    },
    {
      question: 'ćao',
      answer: 'Привет',
    },
    {
      question: 'ćao',
      answer: 'Пока',
    },
    {
      question: 'hvAla',
      answer: 'Спасибо',
    },
    {
      question: 'mOlim',
      answer: 'Пожалуйста (просьба)',
    },
    {
      question: 'izvOlite',
      answer: 'Пожалуйста (ответ)',
    },
    {
      question: 'izvInite',
      answer: 'Извините',
    },
    {
      question: 'izvinJavam se',
      answer: 'Прошу прощения!',
    },
    {
      question: 'Da',
      answer: 'Да',
    },
    {
      question: 'Ne',
      answer: 'Нет',
    },
    {
      question: 'dObro Jutro',
      answer: 'Доброе утро',
    },
    {
      question: 'dObar dan',
      answer: 'Добрый день',
    },
    {
      question: 'dObro vEče',
      answer: 'Добрый вечер',
    },
    {
      question: 'doviđEnja',
      answer: 'До свидания!',
    },
    {
      question: 'da li rAzumété Éngleski?',
      answer: 'До свидания!',
    },
    {
      question: 'dObro',
      answer: 'Хорошо',
    },
    {
      question: 'lOše',
      answer: 'Плохо',
    },
  ],
} as Category;

